<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
	<channel>
		<title>Abeen Bhattacharya</title>
		<description>Semi-Blog of Abeen Bhattacharya. Currently under construction.</description>
		<link>https://www.abeenbhattacharya.com</link>
		<atom:link href="https://www.abeenbhattacharya.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>That one thing</title>
				
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;So, another year of the much-dreaded JEE is over, and a new set of kids will have their faces on buses, and on papers falling off from newspapers. Another set of innocent kids, being forced to take up streams of Engineering they most likely would hate in the upcoming 4 to 5 years, due to some advice from some ‘Sharma-ji ka beta’ ( or perhaps ‘Sharma-ji’ him/her-self ) because that kid too is stuck in the same horrible stream, and wants to console himself of the choices made by him or her earlier. And another set of frustrated parents forcing their kids back to the pathetic education system they dreamt they were finally free off, just because of one screwed up exam.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
				
				<pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
				<link>https://www.abeenbhattacharya.com/jee/2018/06/14/thatonething.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.abeenbhattacharya.com/jee/2018/06/14/thatonething.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>CS Opportunities at IIT Bombay</title>
				
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;This is an article enlisting a number of opportunities in Computer Science you could pursue as an undergraduate at IIT Bombay. It &lt;strong&gt;does not&lt;/strong&gt; talk about career paths in Computer Science &lt;em&gt;after&lt;/em&gt; graduating, rather focusses on what you &lt;strong&gt;can do&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;while you are&lt;/em&gt; an undergraduate at IIT Bombay.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
				
				<pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
				<link>https://www.abeenbhattacharya.com/iitbombay/2018/06/14/CSinIITB.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.abeenbhattacharya.com/iitbombay/2018/06/14/CSinIITB.html</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Are we really at Peace?</title>
				
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;An 18-year-old burns his ass off to clear the three hurdles of science to get into a premier institute of the country (supposedly belonging to the 1% of the nation)&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
				
				<pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
				<link>https://www.abeenbhattacharya.com/random/2017/10/27/KGPSuicide.html</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.abeenbhattacharya.com/random/2017/10/27/KGPSuicide.html</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
